[
    {
      "id": 1,
      "technology": "C",
      "question": "What is the size of int in C?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["2 bytes", "4 bytes", "8 bytes"],
      "correctAnswer": "4 bytes",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "technology": "C",
      "question": "Which loop runs at least once?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["for", "while", "do-while"],
      "correctAnswer": "do-while",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "technology": "C",
      "question": "What is the size of float in C?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["2 bytes", "4 bytes", "8 bytes"],
      "correctAnswer": "4 bytes",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "technology": "C",
      "question": "What is the size of double in C?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["2 bytes", "4 bytes", "8 bytes"],
      "correctAnswer": "8 bytes",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "technology": "C",
      "question": "What is the size of char in C?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["1 bytes", "4 bytes", "8 bytes"],
      "correctAnswer": "1 byte",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
    "technology": "Java",
    "question": "Which of the following is used to create an object in Java?",
    "type": "radio",
    "options": ["new", "create", "object"],
    "correctAnswer": "new",
    "timerDuration": 30
   
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "technology": "Java",
    "question": "Which method is the entry point for a Java program?",
    "type": "radio",
    "options": ["start()", "main()", "run()"],
    "correctAnswer": "main()",
    "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
     "technology": "Java",
    "question": "Which access modifier allows access within the same package?",
    "type": "radio",
    "options": ["private", "protected", "default"],
    "correctAnswer": "default",
    "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "technology": "Java",
    "question": "Which of the following is used for inheritance in Java?",
    "type": "radio",
    "options": ["extends", "implements", "inherits"],
    "correctAnswer": "extends",
    "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "question": "Which company developed JavaScript?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["Netscape", "Microsoft", "Google"],
      "correctAnswer": "Netscape",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "question": "Which of the following is a correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["var myVar;", "int myVar;", "declare myVar;"],
      "correctAnswer": "var myVar;",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a JavaScript data type?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["Number", "String", "Character"],
      "correctAnswer": "Character",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "question": "Which keyword is used to define a constant in JavaScript?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["var", "let", "const"],
      "correctAnswer": "const",
      "timerDuration": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "question": "Which operator is used for strict equality in JavaScript?",
      "type": "radio",
      "options": ["==", "===", "!="],
      "correctAnswer": "===",
      "timerDuration": 30
    }
]
  